Our function is done running.
函数已经运行完毕
So, it looks like that.
看起来
We need to make similar changes to what we had before.
我们需要做出和之前差不多的更改
So, it'll look like this.
改成这样
Get rid of this part.
删掉这部分
Then, this will be the pd pickle.
这个改成 pd.read_pickle
Cool. I'm sorry I didn't move in the fun parts.
好的抱歉 我没有将有趣的部分添加进来
So, if you made it this far,
到目前为止
we now have implemented collaborative filtering.
我们已经实现了协同过滤
Actually, if we look at the all recs portion,
我们来看看 all_recs
solution dot head. I see.
all_recs_sol.head()我知道了
So all recs is a dictionary.
all_recs 是一个字典
So, all recs and all recs solution are dictionaries.
all_recs 和 all_recs_sol 是字典
So if you look at this,
我们来看看这个结果
these are basically the movies read recommend to user two.
这些是向用户 2 推荐的电影
If we look at user eight.
再看看用户 8
Yes. So, here's eight.
是的这是用户 8 的结果
Here's the recommendations we'd give to user eight.
这些是向用户 8 推荐的电影
You can see there's a lot more here.
下面还有很多电影
That's probably just because the individual that was closely matched to
原因可能是第一次与该用户
them the first time had a lot of movies that they watch.
紧密匹配的用户观看了很多电影
It's potentially the reason.
原因可能是这个
Great. So, at the end,
Great最后
we can check some ideas to make sure that we understand them.
我们来回答几个问题 检验下你的理解情况
So, the type of recommendation system you implemented here was actually called
你刚刚实现的推荐系统
collaborative filtering and it was
称为协同过滤
a user-based collaborative filtering because we were comparing users to one another.
它是一个基于用户的协同过滤 因为我们是在相互比较用户
The two methods we use to estimate similarity were
我们衡量相似性时用到的两个方法是
Pearson's correlation coefficient and we used a Euclidean distance.
皮尔逊相关系数和欧几里得距离
So that is e. Then,
所以答案是 e
there was an issue with using the correlation coefficient, what was it?
使用相关系数有个问题 是什么问题？
It was that we were dividing by zero,
问题是我们除以 0
because the spread and some ratings was zero,
因为某些评分的标准差为 0
so h. Use the three objects
所以答案是 h
along with the cells below to correctly fill in the dictionary.
请在以下单元格中使用这三个对象正确填写以下字典
So, for how many pairs of users?
有多少对用户...
This is just making sure that you can use each of the objects that you've created.
这些问题是为了检验你是否会使用你创建的每个对象
So, can we find the users who didn't have any recommendations?
我们能查找没有获得任何推荐的用户吗？
So, we could write a little loop to find that.
我们可以编写一个循环
So, I'll just create this empty list for right now.
我将创建一个暂时为空的列表
Then, for movie recs and all recs items.
for user, movie_recs in all_recs.items()
So, this is a dictionary where the key is
这是一个字典 键是用户
the user and the movie recs are the recommendations.
movie_recs 是推荐电影
Basically, if that list is zero,
如果列表长度为零
then we want to,
我们将...
if there's nothing in that,
如果列表里什么也没有
then what we want to do is append users without recs or append the user.
我们将 users 附加到 users_without_recs
Great. Then, we can look at the length of users without recs.
Great然后查看 users_without_recs 的长度
So it looks like there's 1319.
长度为 1319
How many NaN correlation values were there?
有多少 NaN 系数值？
So, we can find this from the df corrs that we read in.
我们可以使用 df_corrs 得出这个值
We want to find where the movie correlation,
我们要查找有哪些列的
so that was the column where that is a null value.
电影相关系数为 Null 值
So, I got two million.
结果有 200 多万
If you look at this- so, basically,
看看这部分代码
the idea is this is going to count the number
我们将查看该 df_corrs 中
of correlations in the df corrs that were null.
有多少相关系数为 Null
So, this is just going to come back as true or false.
这个的结果为 true 或 false
Then, basically, if we take the sum that's going to count the number of trues.
如果调用 sum() 的话 将返回 true 的数量
We can do the same thing with Euclidean distance.
欧几里得距离也一样
So, that was in df dists and the column was called eucl dists.
对应的是 df_dists 列名为 eucl_dist
So, again, this was a column.
这个也是一列
Similarly, isnull, we look at the sum.
同样 调用 isnull() 然后调用 sum()
This should be zero. So, this is the great part.
结果应该为 0这部分比较重要
When we use the correlation,
当我们使用相关系数时
there were a bunch of incidences where we were dividing by zero.
有很多时候我们除以了 0
A lot of times, that was because the spread of one
这是因为特定用户的
of the ratings for a particular user was zero.
某个近邻的评分标准差为 0
Whereas, when we use a more traditional distance metric like Euclidean distance,
但是如果使用传统距离指标 例如欧几里得距离
instead of a similarity,
而不是相似性指标
we make sure that we don't have any of those issues.
就不会出现这些问题
So, similar to up here.
与这里相似
We can find users with fewer than 10 ratings.
我们也可以查找评分数量少于 10 条的用户
So, I'm just going to copy this users and we'll say less than 10. le10 recs.
复制这段代码 改成 users_lt10_recs
I'll do le10 rex.
这里也是 users_lt10_recs
Basically, if the length
这里应该改成
is less than 10.
如果长度小于 10
So, it looks like that's 1325.
结果是 1325